Duc Dang

IOS Developer

I'm a Junior iOS DEVELOPER. Previously, I had 2 years of experience in Full Stack WEB DEVELOPMENT, before making the switch to iOS. A highly driven individual and a life-long learner. I enjoy solving problems and am very naturally curious, which allows me to learn quickly. I approach everything with a positive attitude and always aims to go above and beyond expectations.



Programming Languages: Swift, JavaScript, C#, Java, Python

Front-End Web Development: HTML5, SCSS

Databases: Apollo/GraphQL, Postgresql

Other Skills: Git, Adobe, Firebase, Mobile Development



Work Experience

2020-05 -Current

IOS Developer

Self-taught, Toronto, Ontario

- Completed online intermediate to advanced iOS courses from Udemy, Raywenderlich and CodewithChris
- Competently, applied core skills (Core Data, SwiftUI, API...) to several App and successfully submitted to Apple Store

2018-10 -2020-04

Junior Full Stack Developer

4D Computer Inc., Arlington, Texas

- Designed and built custom and comprehensive Inventory Management Web Application
- Built front-end user interface using JavaScript libraries such as React and Redux, back-end database using GraphQL and Postgresql



Address

Toronto, ON, M4Y 1H4

Phone

416 678 8385

E-mail

mrtrinh5293@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.co m/in/johndang1/

WWW

http://johntdang.com/

 Collaborated with back-end team to design and launch new features based on customers' feedbacks

2019-02 - Web Developer

2020-01

TrucLam Handmade Co., Hanoi

- Utilized Shopify platform to build and maintain e-commerce website for one of the biggest Vietnamese handmade company
- Edited and uploaded product photographs; designed website front-end for seamless customer experience.

2016-01 - Web Designer Intern

2016-12

OCJ Apparels, Fort Worth, Texas

- Led the initiative to redesign and rebuild the OCJ's website using WordPress and customized it using the WooCommerce platform
- Proposed and took leading role in the implementation of a new inventory management software (Stitch Labs) that double team productivity

Education

2019-09 - Computer Science Diploma: Computer

Current Science

Centennial College - Toronto, Canada

2016-09 - Bachelor of Arts: Information And Communication Technology

The University Of Texas At Arlington - Arlington, Texas



English

French

Vietnamese



2018-08 Full Stack Web Developer